Guide to the Carla Stellweg Papers M1752
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 5. Publications
  - Consultation and Research
    - Arte en Mesoamerica [Artmedia] (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Bolivia (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Brazil (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Chile (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Chile (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Chile (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Chile (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Chile (Flat-box 96, Folder 5)
    - Colombia (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Colombia (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Colombia (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Colombia (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Colombia (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Colombia (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Colombia (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Colombia (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Colombia (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Colombia (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Colombia (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - [Colombia] (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Costa Rica (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Costa Rica (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - [Cuba] (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - [Cuba] (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - [Cuba] (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - [Cuba] (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - [Cuba] (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - [Cuba] - Center for Cuban Studies publications, 1988-1991 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - [Cuba] - Center for Cuban Studies publications, 1991-1992 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - [Cuba] - Center for Cuban Studies publications, 1994-1995 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Dominican Republic (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Ecuador (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Latino and Latin American artists (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Latino and Latin American press clippings (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - [Latino and Latin American press clippings] (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - [Latino and Latin American press clippings], 1988-1989 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - [Latino and Latin American press clippings], 1990-1994 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - [Latino and Latin American press clippings], 1991-1996 (Flat-box 94, Folder 1)
    - [Latino and Latin American press clippings], 1995-1999 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - [Latino and Latin American press clippings], 2000-2009 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - [Mexico] (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - [Mexico] (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - [Mexico] (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - [Mexico] (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - [Mexico] (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - [Mexico] (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - [Mexico] (Flat-box 96, Folder 4)
    - Mexico, 1990s (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Mexico, 1990s (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Mexico, 1990s (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Mexico, 1990s (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Mexico, 1990s (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Mexico, 1990s (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - [Mexico, includes correspondence] (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - [Mexico - Marco folders with art prints and correspondence] (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - [Mexico] - "Mexico: The Energy Sector" (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - [Mexico] - Path of Echoes (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - [Mexico] - U.S./Latin Trade, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - [Mexico] - U.S./Latin Trade, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - [Mexico] - U.S./Latin Trade, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - [Mexico] - U.S./Latin Trade, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - [Mexico] - U.S./Latin Trade, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - [Mexico] - U.S./Latin Trade, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - [Mexico] - U.S./Latin Trade, 1996 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - [Mexico] - Latin Trade (formerly U.S./Latin Trade ), 1996 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - [Mexico] - Latin Trade (formerly U.S./Latin Trade ), 1996 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Panama (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Peru (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Puerto Rico (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Uera del Capitalismo and Revista de Revista (Flat-box 92, Folder 5)
    - Uruguay (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Venezuela (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - [Venezuela] (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - [Venezuela] (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - [Venezuela] (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - [Venezuela] (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - [Venezuela] (Box 88, Folder 9)
- Series 6. Personal and Biographical Information
  This series is mainly comprised of publications and clippings that mention Stellweg. Other materials include correspondence, awards, and poetry. Stellweg's resume can be found in the folder JM [Jewish Museum] file (Box 72, Folder 6) from Series 2.
  - Txts-interviews - Mentions of Carla Stellweg (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Letters re: Carla's qualifications (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - [Letter to Stellweg with artwork/drawings] (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Conectamos, con los ojos - Photomontaje fuerte y surreal - Tan bella es tu mirada (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - [Publications mentioning Stellweg] (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - [Publications mentioning Stellweg] (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Texts - Mentions Carla Stellweg [contains pencil drawing] (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - [Awards - Certificate from ATLI] (Box 101, Item 3)
  - [Awards - Certificate of achievement for communication and leadership], 1998 (Box 101, Item 4)
  - [Awards - Certificate of completion for the Executive Leadership Institute from the Nonprofit Resource Center of Texas], 1999 (Box 101, Item 5)
  - [Awards - Plaque from the Board of Directors of Blue Star], 2000 (Box 101, Item 6)
- Series 7. Photographic Materials
  This series is divided into three subseries (Photographs, Negatives, and Slides) based on the format of material. The series includes images of exhibitions and artwork, as well as some personal photographs. Many of the images are individually labeled. Photographic materials can be found throughout the collection where indicated.
  - Photographs
    - Arco-Madrid [includes negatives], 1997 Feb (Box 90, Folder 18)
    - C.S. Cia. Sociales (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Dialogues of Peace [includes negatives], 1995 Jul (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Fashion-modeling photos C.S., 1960s-1970s (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - La Agencia Stell-Seggall CS Gallery + other venues install shots - [Traces of Memory, includes negatives] (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - La Agencia Stell-Seggall CS Gallery + other venues install shots - C. Garaicoa [includes negatives] (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Russians exhibition (Leonid Pinchersky) when CS Gallery had Bway Space [includes negatives] (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - [Photo Album - Exhibits, Detalle (includes slides)] (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Pride of India Gen'l Ledger [ledger and photo album] (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Negatives
    - C.S. Cia. Sociales - Trip to intro Spencer Throck Morton-Mex (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - C.S. Cia. Sociales - More Spencer + me in Mex City - Cubans (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - C.S. Cia. Sociales - More Spencer + me in Mex City (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - C.S. Cia. Sociales - In Mexico w/ P. Sloane, BEA, 1980s (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - C.S. Cia. Sociales - Bellport 1990s Long Island - Levine (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - C.S. Cia. Sociales - Renovating loft for gallery walls, 1990 (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - C.S. Cia. Sociales - W/ Cathy de Zegher + Mex Venezuela (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - C.S. Cia. Sociales - W/ Cathy de Zegher C.A. trip, 1990s (Box 90, Folder 16)
    - Pan American artists CS Gallery (Box 90, Folder 17)
  - Slides
    - [Argentina] - From "Pictorica" (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - C.S. Cia. Sociales (Box 91, Folder 32)
    - Cuban artists - J. Bedia, Cuban cat-box (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Cuban artists - Luis Cruz Azaceta (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Cuban artists - Carlos R. Cardenas (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - La Agencia Stell-Seggall CS Gallery + other venues install shots - "Traces of Memory," May 8-29, 1993 and Living Rites, June 5-26, 1993, 1993 May-Jun (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - La Agencia Stell-Seggall CS Gallery + other venues install shots - Jesse Amado (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - La Agencia Stell-Seggall CS Gallery + other venues install shots - Luis Camnitzer (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - La Agencia Stell-Seggall CS Gallery + other venues install shots - Carlos Capelan [includes photographs] (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - La Agencia Stell-Seggall CS Gallery + other venues install shots - A. Elizond (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - La Agencia Stell-Seggall CS Gallery + other venues install shots - N. Garcia Ferraz (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - La Agencia Stell-Seggall CS Gallery + other venues install shots - L.M. Gordillo (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - La Agencia Stell-Seggall CS Gallery + other venues install shots - S. Gruner (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - La Agencia Stell-Seggall CS Gallery + other venues install shots - Arturo Herrera (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - La Agencia Stell-Seggall CS Gallery + other venues install shots - Clemencia Labin (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - La Agencia Stell-Seggall CS Gallery + other venues install shots - David Lamelas (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - La Agencia Stell-Seggall CS Gallery + other venues install shots - Diego Medina (Box 91, Folder 16)
    - La Agencia Stell-Seggall CS Gallery + other venues install shots - R. Mendieta (Box 91, Folder 17)
    - La Agencia Stell-Seggall CS Gallery + other venues install shots - Miguel Rojas (Box 91, Folder 18)
    - La Agencia Stell-Seggall CS Gallery + other venues install shots - J. Palacios (Box 91, Folder 19)
    - La Agencia Stell-Seggall CS Gallery + other venues install shots - A. Patino (Box 91, Folder 20)
    - La Agencia Stell-Seggall CS Gallery + other venues install shots - Kukuli + Eugenia installation (Box 91, Folder 21)
    - Latino/Chicano artists - Carlos Almaraz (Box 91, Folder 22)
    - Latino/Chicano artists - Yreina D. Cervanez (Box 91, Folder 23)
    - Latino/Chicano artists - Gronk (Box 91, Folder 24)
    - Latino/Chicano artists - R. Juarez (Box 91, Folder 25)
    - Latino/Chicano artists - Pedro Lujan (Box 91, Folder 26)
    - Latino/Chicano artists - Enrique Martinez Celaya (Box 91, Folder 27)
    - Latino/Chicano artists - Arnaldo Roche (Box 91, Folder 28)
    - Latino/Chicano artists - Frank Romero (Box 91, Folder 29)
    - Latino/Chicano artists - John Valadez (Box 91, Folder 30)
    - Latino/Chicano artists - Jesus Bautista Moroles [includes correspondence and publications] (Box 91, Folder 31)
    - Pan American artists CS Gallery - Ana Mercedes Hoyos, Colombia (Box 91, Folder 33)
    - Pan American artists CS Gallery - Pablo Schugurensky, Argentina (Box 91, Folder 34)
    - Pan American artists CS Gallery - J. Davidovich (Box 91, Folder 35)
    - Pan American artists CS Gallery - Liliana Porter (Box 91, Folder 36)
    - Pan American artists CS Gallery - Luis Stand (Box 91, Folder 37)
    - Pan American artists CS Gallery - A.M. Maiolino [includes photographs] (Box 91, Folder 38)
    - Pan American artists CS Gallery - Sergio Vega (Box 91, Folder 39)
    - Pan American artists CS Gallery - Cecilia Vicuna (Box 91, Folder 40)
    - Pan American artists CS Gallery -"Inside Art" [New York Times article in binder with slides and negatives] (Box 91, Folder 41)
    - Rooted Visions (Box 91, Folder 42)
    - Soul Catchers (Box 91, Folder 43)
- Series 8. Audiovisual Materials
  This series includes video and sound recordings of lectures, performances and artwork. Formats include VHS tapes, audiocassettes, microcassettes, DVDs, Mini DVs, and records.
  - Retablo's (Box 99, Videotape 1)
  - Learning Designs/WNET - Behind the Scenes with David Hockney (Pilot), 1988 (Box 99, Videotape 2)
  - Promocional Pasion por Friday Stock (Box 99, Videotape 3)
  - Kukuli Velarde Performance Piece (Box 99, Videotape 4)
  - Maria Elena Gonzalez Assemblage Composite Neuberger Museum -Suny Purchase - NY, 1994 Jul-Sep (Box 99, Videotape 5)
  - 1) Regina Vater Video - 6 Pieces 2) Les Levine: Close Frenzies 1986, Anxiety Religion + Art 1985, Einstein: Nuclear Comedy 1983 3) Gary Perkins, 1983-1986 (Box 99, Videotape 6)
  - Xavier Blum, 1986-1987 (Box 99, Videotape 7)
  - Xavier Blum (Box 99, Videotape 8)
  - Ligorano/Reese Installations, 1991-1993 (Box 99, Videotape 9)
  - E.A. Diaz... (Box 99, Videotape 10)
  - Eloy Tarcisio - Un Concepto de Identidad, 1990 (Box 99, Videotape 11)
  - Chakaia Booker (Box 99, Videotape 12)
  - "El Mercado Del Arte Latinoamericano Hoy" Martes 26 de Sep: Carla Stellweg (Box 100, Videotape 1)
  - "El Mercado Del Arte Latinoamericano Hoy" Miercoles 27 de Sep: Carlos Ashida (Box 100, Videotape 2)
  - Root Visions Symposium, 1988 (Box 100, Videotape 3)
  - Alejandro Nieto Lorez - Cali (Colombia) - Instalaciones, 1994-1995 (Box 100, Videotape 4)
  - Presidental Debates (Box 100, Videotape 5)
  - Rolando Pena (Box 100, Videotape 6)
  - Smell of Fish - Josely Carualho (Box 100, Videotape 7)
  - "The Butcher Shop of Divine Providence: Act III from the Opera 'The Triumphs of War'" (Box 100, Videotape 8)
  - Mary Beth Edelson - SVA [Mini DV], 2005 Dec 5 (Box 100, Videotape 9)
  - Carla Slide Lecture - SVA [Mini DV], 2005 Dec 5 (Box 100, Videotape 10)
  - Class Carla SVA-Dub (for Mary Beth) [Mini DV] (Box 100, Videotape 11)
  - [Unlabeled 8mm video cassette] (Box 100, Videotape 12)
  - Ouzo [microcassette] (Box 100, Audiocassette 1)
  - [Ouzo, microcassette] (Box 100, Audiocassette 2)
  - [Ouzo, microcassette] (Box 100, Audiocassette 3)
  - Over-We Cuevacivac [microcassette, grouped with "Mary Beth Edelson -SVA" and "Carla Slide Lecture - SVA"] (Box 100, Audiocassette 4)
  - Luis Camnitzer Interview (Box 100, Audiocassette 5)
  - Pilar Anarca Rodriguez (Box 100, Audiocassette 6)
  - Happy New Year! Astrology Chart Carla (by Nauicke?), 2002 Jan 12 (Box 100, Audiocassette 7)
  - Regina Vater (Box 100, Audiocassette 8)
  - [Unlabeled audiocassette] (Box 100, Audiocassette 9)
  - Sepstanikas Inferno - Le Fresnoy [DVD], 2004 (Box 100, Compact disc 1)
  - Damir [Niksic?] [DVD] (Box 100, Compact disc 2)
  - You Kill Me - WBX Show Hans Breder (Teacher Ana Mendieta) [DVD] (Box 100, Compact disc 3)
  - You Kill Me Trailer [DVD] (Box 100, Compact disc 4)
  - The Drill - Hans Breder [DVD] (Box 100, Compact disc 5)
  - Manana [record] (Box 100, Item 1)
- Series 9. Financial Records (Restricted)
  - Financial records (Restricted) (9 folders) (Box 102)
  - Financial records (Restricted) (7 folders) (Box 103)
  - Financial records (Restricted) (6 folders) (Box 104)
- Series 10. Accession 2015-145. Additional Materials
  The accession consists of materials that were received at a later date than the rest of the collection. It contains materials that are related to other materials in the collection.
  The accession documents Stellweg's professional activities as a curator, and director of various art galleries and museums, including her work at the Carla Stellweg Gallery, the Stellweg-Seguy Gallery, the Museum of Contemporary Hispanic Art (MOCHA), the Rufino Tamayo Museum, Blue Star Art Space, and White Box. The accession also documents her professional activities as a consultant and speaker for publications, seminars, symposiums, exhibitions and gallery shows. Additionally the accession contains information on artists, many of whom Carla Stellweg represented and whose artwork she sold.
  Materials include correspondence, documentation on artists and exhibitions, catalogs, art auction catalogs, exhibition invitations, appointment books, administrative records, pricelists, invoices, loan agreements, drafts of presentations, and research material for Stellweg’s consultation and curatorial work.
  Among other formats, this accession contains photographs, slides, negatives, microcassettes, VHS tapes, CDs, DVDs, and a hard-drive. The images include exhibitions and artwork as well as personal photographs. Many of the images are individually labeled.
  Many of the files have been kept in their original order with original folder headings and original descriptive notes.
  - Memberships and invites, 2009-2012 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Ben Kinmont materials from his show at New York University's Fales Library, 2011-2012 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    Ben Kinmont is an artist whose work is archives-based.
  - Exhibition brochures and catalogs, 2004-2012 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    Stack of valuable exhibition brochures and catalogs that were used by Carla Stellweg for other related topics-projects.
  - Exhibition brochures and catalogs (part 1 of 2), 2006-2012 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Exhibition brochures and catalogs (part 2 of 2), 2006-2012 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Various artists and shows of interests (part 1 of 4), 2008-2015 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    Various artists and shows of interest (including various art fairs and auction news, such as Frieze, American Gay Life, The Armory at Park Avenue, PAPERSHOW.ORG - an exhibition of alternative printed zines and papers in the Museum of Modern Art’s Education Department’s exhibition plus miscellaneous material archives, along with additional Ana Mendieta information, including program and invites for the Katherine E. Nash Gallery exhibit, Covered in Time and History: The Films of Ana Mendieta, as well as Galerie Lelong’s event for her death anniversary. Possibly related to other Ana Mendieta materials in Box 15.
  - Various artists and shows of interests (part 2 of 4), 2008-2015 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Various artists and shows of interests (part 3 of 4), 2008-2015 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Various artists and shows of interests (part 4 of 4), 2008-2015 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Various invites of interest, 2013-2015 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Additional certificates and awards - Instituto Tecnológico de Monterrey and others, 2009-2012 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Archive Salón Independiente, Mexico D.F. and Galeria Pecanins posters and invites, 1969-1970, 2010 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Thank you letters from various Interns and Staff - White Box and other projects, 2002-2015 (Box 106, Folder 7)
    Related Materials
    Related to materials in Box 9.
    Includes correspondence and a Compact Disc.
  - Page of slides from the Stellweg-Seguy Gallery's group exhibition, Soul Catchers, including shots of installation pieces by artists David Mach and B. Wurtz, 1990-1991 (Box 106, Folder 8)
    Related to materials in Box 15.
  - Banamex Grant acceptance letter, 1993 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Wolf Vostell catalog, Sala de Exposiciones del Museo Español de Arte Contemporaneo, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 10)
    Artes Visuales Issue #24, May 1980 centerfold has Wolf Vostell Desastres (Disasters) 1972, pp. 44-45 – Caused Advertisers to Claim Artes Visuales engaged in “Pornographic” representation of contemporary art. Carla Stellweg Editorial reply was published in Artes Visuales Issue #26, November 1980. Related to materials in Box 11.
  - Magenta Magazine contributor's invite, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    Related to materials in Box 12
  - La Regla Rota 4, Spring, 1987 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Additional preparatory materials for Latin American Spirit, book and exhibition about Rubens Gerchman and Julio Le Parc, 1980-1991 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    Related to materials in Box 18
  - Tomás Ybarra-Fausto - Rockefeller Foundation, 2005 (Box 107, Folder 4)
    Related to materials in Box 25
  - Chuck Ramirez - Blue Star Contemporary Art Center Board member and artist, 2011 (Box 107, Folder 5)
    Chuck Ramirez was a board member at Blue Star Contemporary Art Center and a successful artist. He was the prime advocate to have Carla Stellweg become Blue Star’s first professional executive director & chief curator – prior to then Blue Star had been an artist-run alternative space founded in July of 1985. The anniversary of its founding became a Citywide celebration titled “San Antonio Contemporary Art Month”. Related to materials in Box 26.
  - Correspondence, 2002-2012 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    Related to materials in Box 27
  - Finnish art show, The Far Away, Nearby, curated by Carla Stellweg, 2004-2005 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    Related to materials in Box 28
    Includes catalogs, correspondence and a Compact Disc.
  - White Box DVDs - Damir Niksic's, If I Wasn't a Muslim, and Andre Sier's, Of Selected Works, 2004-2008 (Box 107, Folder 8)
    Materials used for White Box’s exhibition entitled, STREAM in 2007. Related to materials in Box 28. Includes Digital Video Discs.
  - Specificity of Place: Longing and Belonging - Presentation on Oh Chi-Gyun, 2008 (Box 107, Folder 9)
    Related to materials in Box 28.
  - Carla Stellweg essay on Documenta IX, Kassel, Germany - published in Art Nexus, 1992 (Box 107, Folder 10)
    Related to materials in Box 46.
  - Carla Stellweg essay on Documenta XII, Kassel, Germany, 2007 (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Art and Surveillance - Carla Stellweg keynote speech at the Instituto Tecnológico de Monterrey, Mexico (2008), 1991-2008 (Box 107, Folder 12)
    Digital supplement: PowerPoint Presentation.
  - El Arte y la Escultura en Plata: Moderno o Vanguardia? - Carla Stellweg presentation at Museo de Arte Moderno, Mexico D.F. (2009), 2009-2012 (Box 107, Folder 13)
    This presentation was for the launching of Silver Seduction, the Art of Mexican Modernist Antonio Pineda, an exhibition and book published by The Fowler Museum, UCLA, California, curated by Gobi Stromberg. Includes a Compact Disc.
  - Congresso Internacional Utopia: Espacios Alternitivos y Expressiones Culturales en America Latina, Monterrey, Mexico, Carla Stellweg presentation entitled, Hoy es El Futuro de Ayer o Ayer fue el Futuro de Hoy?, 2010 (Box 107, Folder 14)
    Digital supplement: images used in the PowerPoint presentation made on site.
  - Carla Stellweg presentation for Ann Indych-Lopez's book, Muralism Without Walls, at America's Society, 2010 (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - Patricia Ortiz Monasterio - El Mercado del Arte Latinoamericano Hoy, September 25, 1995 (Card-box 108, Videotape 1)
    Videotapes 1, 2 and 3 are all from a symposium on the Latin American Art Market organized by Eduardo Rubio in Monterrey, Mexico. Related to materials in Box 30.
  - Fernando Gutierrez - El Mercado del Arte Latinoamericano Hoy. September 28, 1995 (Card-box 108, Videotape 2)
  - Ana y Teresa Iturralde - El Mercado del Arte Latinoamericano Hoy, September 29, 1995 (Card-box 108, Videotape 3)
  - Abraham Cruzvillegas – selected VERY EARLY performance pieces in situ, Mexico City monuments, 1992 (Card-box 108, Videotape 4)
  - Kukuli Velarde + Eugenia Vargas Show, Carla Stellweg Gallery on Broadway, Soho – amateur video done by gallery friend of Anna Indych-Lopez & Angel Lopez, 1994-1995 (Card-box 108, Videotape 5)
  - Microcassette interview with Juan Downey, undated (Card-box 108, Audiocassette 6)
    Microcassette interviews with various arts professionals, VERY VALUABLE!
  - Microcassette interviews with Nohra Haime and Mary-Anne Martin, 1988 (Card-box 108, Audiocassette 7)
  - Microcassette interviews with Mauricio Quintana and Pierre Levai, 1988 (Card-box 108, Audiocassette 8)
  - Microcassette interview with Milton Esterow, 1988 (Card-box 108, Audiocassette 9)
  - Microcassette interview with Liliana Porter, undated (Card-box 108, Audiocassette 10)
  - Microcassette interview with Jaime Palacios, undated (Card-box 108, Audiocassette 11)
  - Microcassette interview with Jaime Davidovich, undated (Card-box 108, Audiocassette 12)
  - Microcassette interview with Yishai Judisman, 1988 (Card-box 108, Audiocassette 13)
  - Microcassette interview with Leandro Katz, undated (Card-box 108, Audiocassette 14)
  - Microcassette interviews with Nohra Haime and Herstand, 1988 (Card-box 108, Audiocassette 15)
  - Microcassette interview with Quik, 1984 (Card-box 108, Audiocassette 16)
  - Microcassette interview with Ortiz - N.J., undated (Card-box 108, Audiocassette 17)
  - Microcassette interviews with R. Ortiz and A. Greco, undated (Card-box 108, Audiocassette 18)
  - Microcassette of Cactus Bra Space, undated (Card-box 108, Audiocassette 19)
  - Microcassette 2nd tape, undated (Card-box 108, Audiocassette 20)
  - Microcassette interview with G. Ranoff [?], undated (Card-box 108, Audiocassette 21)
  - Microcassette interview with Carolee Schneemann, 1999 (Card-box 108, Audiocassette 22)
  - Carla Stellweg microcassette, undated (Card-box 108, Audiocassette 23)
  - [unlabeled microcassette], undated (Card-box 108, Audiocassette 24)
  - [unlabeled microcassette], undated (Card-box 108, Audiocassette 25)
  - El Arte Simulacral del Fetiche Critico, review of the show at CA2M, Madrid, Spain, 2010 (Box 109, Folder 1)